

Anish Maharjan

Date of birth: 19/10/1995

Nationality: Nepalese

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Klaneettitie 1 B 049 00420 HELSINKI, Finland (Home)

anishmhn@hotmail.com

(+358) 0452475064

https://github.com/ anish0123 (GitHub)

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/anish-maharjan1/

https://gitlab.metropolia.fi/ anishm (GitLab)

ABOUT ME

Goal-oriented, motivated, hardworking student targeting to gain experience and build a career in the Information and Technology sector. Supports team administrative, project coordination, design, and programming needs. Basic Knowledge of Java, C#, JavaScript, Nodejs, MySQL, Kotlin, React and React Native. School projects included building apps, optimising programs, and validating code.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

22/08/2021 - CURRENT Espoo

Bachelors in Information and Technology Metropolia University of Applied Sciences

Address Karaportti 2, Espoo | Website www.metropolia.fi

18/09/2016 - 04/05/2020 Espoo, Finland

Bachelors in Business Administration Laurea University of Applied Sciences

Address Vanha maantie 9, Espoo, Finland | Website www.laurea.fi

WORK EXPERIENCE

22/07/2020 - CURRENT Helsinki, Finland

Diagnostics and Preparation Coach Swappie Oy

- Providing training and support to members of team.
- Recording the data of received materials.
- Running diagnostics of refurbished phones.
- Repairing of refurbished phones

13/10/2017 - 21/07/2020 Vantaa, Finland

Counter Employee HMSHost Finland Oy

- Handling customers and cash through the cash counter.
- Providing meals to the customers.
- Waiting tables and serving customers.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Nepali

Other language(s):

English

Listening C1	Reading C1	Spoken production C1	Spoken interaction C1	Writing C1
			<u> </u>	

Finnish

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
A2	A2	production	interaction	A2
		B1	B1	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Figma & Adobe XD | GIT , GITHUB | NodeJS - REST API Design and Development | Microsoft , Microsoft Office | Adobe Creative Cloud (Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign) | CCNAv7 - Introduction to Networks

DATABASES

MySql/MariaDB | ROOM Database PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

JavaScript | React,React Native | Java | C# | Web: HTML, CSS | Kotli n | Nodejs and expressJS